http://www.divsys.com/component/content/article/54-privacy-policy

AboutLab TestingRapidProtoQualityContact us
DIVSYS.com
Privacy Policy
| Print |
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When
ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.
You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information? We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal
information. Do we use cookies? Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third party sites have
separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site
and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause
we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in
compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We
therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.As part of the California Online
Privacy Protection Act, all registered users of our site may make any
changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control
panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and Conditions Please
also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our
website at http://www.divsys.comYour Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 10/11/2010Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.divsys.com8110 Zionsville RoadIndianapolis, Indiana 46268 U.S.A.
This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it
Email: sales@divsys.com Web: www.divsys.com DIVSYS Contact Form
© Copyright 2010 DIVSYS International, LLCPrivacy Policy | Terms of Use
